outerplaces.com 2018-06-24

# Privacy Policy - Outer Places

This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of Outer Places, LLC including our affiliate divisions such as Supply Pod and other mystery box programs ("we", "our" or "us").

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose and transfer the information you provide when you interact with us including (but not limited to) via our websites and downloadable applications that link to this policy ("online services").

This policy also tells you how we use tracking technologies, cookies and browsing data we collect from your use of the online services, the measures we take to protect the security of the information you provide to us through the online services, and how you can contact us if you have any questions regarding the online services (including if you want to unsubscribe from our services or update your contact details).

* ## SCOPE AND CONSENT

When you use the online services, you are contracting with Outer Places, LLC. If you reside outside of the United States, Outer Places, LLC is your data controller. By using the online services, you expressly consent to our collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

* ## TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Our goal is to collect and use information to deliver effective and personalized services which take your interests and preferences into account, as well as for our legitimate business needs and interests.

There are two main types of information we collect about users of our online services that include (but are not limited to) the following:

  * Information that identifies you: This is commonly referred to as "personal information" and includes, for example, information that you provide to us such as your name, home address, age, gender, telephone number, e¬mail address, payment information (including your credit card number), and/or photos or video footage of you; and

  * Information that relates to you, but on its own does not identify you: Such as information about your Internet connection, the equipment you use to access our online services and information relating to your usage of those services.

There are six main categories of information we collect about users of our online services users that include (but are not limited to) the following:

  * Contact/Registration information: for example, your telephone number or e¬mail address, where you have subscribed to a service such as program updates; name, age, gender or interests when you register for an account on one of our online services; delivery address where you are buying a product or service through an online service; or your age, location, e-mail address or delivery address if you choose to enter a competition or sweepstakes offered through the online services.

  * Transaction information: when you order products or services through the online services, you may provide information such as your credit / debit card number, expiration date verification number and other personal information related to that transaction.

  * Information that you provide on message boards and other user forums: including your username, e-mail address, images or videos. Please use caution when posting to messages boards or other forums, as information posted to these portions of the online services is public information.

  * Information about your equipment: for example, the type and version of your device’s operating system or web browser, your device ID, and in some instances, your device’s location.

  * Information about your interactions with the online services: for example, your Internet protocol or (IP) address, pages that you visit within the online services, gameplay data or other information collected through Cookies and Tracking Technologies

  * Information that is collected from social networks and publicly available data: if you visit our online services on a device through which you also interact with social networks or if you interact with us through a social media function such as a plug-in (for example, a Facebook "like" button) then you may be permitting us to have on¬going access to some information from your social network profile (such as your name, email address, your friend list, photo, age, gender, location, birthday, social networking ID, current city, the people/sites you follow, and so forth). If you don’t want a social network to collect the information about you as described above, or you don’t want to a social network to share it with us and other third parties, please review the privacy settings and instructions of the applicable social network before you visit and use our online services.

We may also receive other information (e.g., content viewed and information about the advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on, etc.) from your interaction with the online services. You agree that we may share information concerning your content consumption and video viewing with, or obtain information about your content consumption and video viewing from, analytics providers and advertising partners and third-party social media sites unless you withdraw your consent. The information we have access to from the third-party services varies by service and is controlled by your privacy settings on that service and by your consent. Information that may be passed to analytics providers and advertising partners may be done so via cookies and tracking technologies. By associating an account managed by a third party with your Outer Places, LLC account and authorizing us to have access to this information, you agree that we may collect, use, and store information from third-party services in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

* ## HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION

We collect your information when you use our online services in three main ways:

  * Directly from you, when you provide it to us: for example, when you request products or services from us, when you register with us, respond to surveys, contact us or otherwise interact with us. Please remember that if others use devices into which you remain logged in, they may share information with us as if they were you, and they may have access to information that you have previously provided us. To protect your privacy, please log out from the online services you use from shared devices.

  * Automatically, when you use our online services: we collect information through the use of cookies and other technologies.

  * From third parties including social networks, other online services, from publicly available records, and from our trusted business partners.

* ## CONTESTS, QUESTIONS OR SURVEYS

When you ask a question, participate in a survey or enter a contest or sweepstakes, we may collect your name, address, phone number and e-mail address. We use this information to administer your participation in a contest or sweepstakes. At the time you are entering a contest or sweepstakes, we may ask your permission to send you future marketing information.

* ## HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

  * provide the services you have requested, including sweepstakes, contests or promotions

  * create an online services account if you have requested one

  * personalize the services offered by us or our affiliates, including providing personalized advertising on some online services

  * respond to your inquiries, requests, and comments

  * allow you to participate in the interactive features of our online services, where you choose to do so

  * provide technical support for the online services

  * prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities (including copyright infringement) on the online services

  * protect the safety of users and others on the online services

  * enforce our online services’ terms of service

  * understand how online services are used so that we can continuously improve them, and the services we provide to you

  * send you service-related communications, including announcements and administrative messages

  * send you newsletters and information about products, services and promotions relating to us and/or our business partners or other organizations that we work with, in accordance with your communication preferences. Subject to legal restrictions (including consent where necessary) we may also use technology (such as Facebook Custom Audiences) to deliver advertising to you on other sites based on the email address or other personal information you provided to us or through the use of information we received from third parties.

  * if you use an Outer Places, LLC e­commerce website to send gifts, we may use the email addresses that you provide to send your gifts, provide other communications relating to such transaction, as well as any further communications as may be authorized by the recipients

  * implement social networking features you have activated; and

  * we may combine all the information we collect or receive about you for any of the foregoing purposes.

* ## HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

Information shared among Outer Places, LLC affiliates:

  * When you choose to register for an account on any Outer Places, LLC online service: the information you provide may be shared with Outer Places, LLC affiliates and used to help us better tailor our services, products and advertising to you. Note that you may be registered for different accounts with different Outer Places, LLC group companies or in different areas of our business. Please visit the account settings page of the applicable online service if you wish you "de­register" from your account or for more information, or email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#bcd5d2dad3fcd3c9c8d9ceccd0dddfd9cf92dfd3d1)

  * Information collected automatically: this information collected from your interaction with the online services via Cookies and Tracking Technologies, which may or may not include personal information, may be shared with Outer Places, LLC affiliates for the purposes of research, analysis, marketing and ad-serving.

Information shared with trusted third parties:

  * Service providers or business partners that we have retained to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf: Such as for research and analytics, hosting websites, fulfilling transactions, maintaining databases, administering contests, providing technology services and platforms, and processing payments. These parties are provided only with the personal information or other information they need to perform their functions and can only use and disclose that information as is necessary to perform the services on our behalf, or to comply with legal requirements. We take steps to ensure that third-party service providers will take appropriate steps to protect your personal information.

  * Social Networks: You may interact with certain features of the online services that cause information to be published to your social networks. For example, you may click on a Facebook "like" button, which publishes to your Facebook account that you "like" one of our TV shows or movies. On pages of the online services that contain social network functionality, the social network providing the functionality may be able to collect information about you, even if you don’t use that functionality. For example, if a page within the online services contains a Facebook "like" button, Facebook may be able to collect data about your visit to that page, even if you don’t click on the "like" button. To control this sharing of information, please review the privacy policy of the relevant social network and/or log out of it before you use the online services.

Information we share with advertisers (including Targeted Advertising):

  * Some online services may be supported with advertising, and collect data to help the online services serve ads. This helps keep the cost of online services low or free.

  * We may work with advertisers and third-party advertising networks, who may receive information about how you interact with advertising provided in the online service. We may also work with consumer data resellers that buy and/or sell information to other companies for multiple purposes including offering products and services that may interest you. These third parties may view, edit or set their own tracking technologies/cookies. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. They might also obtain information about other applications that you have downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit and other information about you or your device in order to analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the online services and elsewhere.

Information shared with other parties  
In addition, we may disclose your personal information collected through the online services to law enforcement agencies, government/regulatory bodies, and content protection organizations to:

  * Protect our legal rights, privacy or safety, and those of our subsidiaries, affiliates, employees, agents and contractors or other individuals;

  * Protect the safety and security of visitors to our online services or other properties;

  * Protect against fraud or other illegal activity or for risk management purposes;

  * Respond to inquiries or requests from government, regulatory, law enforcement or public authorities;

  * Permit us to pursue available remedies, commence, participate in, or defend litigation, or limit the damages that we may sustain;

  * Comply with the law including with subpoenas, search warrants, court orders, and other legal process; or

  * Enforce applicable terms of service

Sale or transfer of all or part of our business or assets   
We reserve the right to transfer your usage information and personal information in the event we sell or transfer all or a part of our business or assets so that the buyer can continue to offer you the online services. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide you with reasonable notice of such transfer, or as otherwise required by law. If you do not want your personal information to be processed following such a transfer, you should contact the subsequent owner of the business.

* ## WHO MAY USE THIS WEB SITE 

  * Except where otherwise indicated we do not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be fully familiar with the online services used by their children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child under 13 has provided us with information without his or her consent, he or she should contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3e575058517e514b4a5b4c4e525f5d5b4d105d5153) As required by law, we will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

  * For certain websites covered by this Privacy Policy and involved in e-commerce (for example, [http://www.getsupplypod.com](http://www.getsupplypod.com/) you may only be able to use that site and any related services if you are 18 years of age or older, or the age of majority in your jurisdiction of residence, whichever is older. If you are under the age of 18 or the age of majority in your jurisdiction of residence, you may only use that site and any related services with the involvement of a parent or legal guardian.

California minors under 18 years old may request the removal of any information that they posted to Outer Places, LLC sites by contacting [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#11787f777e517e64657463617d707274623f727e7c). Upon such request, Outer Places, LLC will anonymize or remove from public view any content posted by a minor to one of its websites, unless required by law to retain such content or information.

This Website is intended for users from the United States and those not governed by privacy policies of other countries. Information sent to us will be processed and housed on servers located in the U.S. and in other countries. In some cases, we may process personal information on servers located outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process Personal Information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners. Do not send us information unless you consent to the application of U.S and other countries’ laws and to the use and disclosure of your information consistent with this Privacy Policy

* ## HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We maintain procedural, technical and physical safeguards for our online services to help protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personal information you provide via our online services. We also ask the service providers that help us deliver our online services to so the same. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our online services. Unfortunately, no transmission of data is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. Therefore, any transmission of personal information to us is made at your own risk. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us using the contact details below.

Usernames & Passwords

It is important that you protect and maintain the security of any account and that you notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of any Outer Places, LLC account. Do not disclose your password to anyone else.

* ## YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES

Communication Preferences and Opt-outs

If you have subscribed to one or more of our email newsletters or are receiving them from us and you don’t want them anymore, you can unsubscribe. Select the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any message, by other means provided to unsubscribe, or using the contact details below, to unsubscribe from marketing and promotional e-mails and associated marketing delivered to you on third party services based on your subscription data. There are certain service-related messages other than advertising, marketing, promotional or telemarketing materials, however, for which you cannot unsubscribe without unsubscribing to our services in their entirety. 

Access and Correction

In addition to the functionality provided to you via the online services, where legally required we provide online visitors with access to their personal information and the ability to review, update and correct it. To help your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, and possibly photo ID before granting access to your personal information. Please contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#afc6c1c9c0efc0dadbcadddfc3cecccadc81ccc0c2) for more information about exercising these rights.

Data Retention and Deletion

We will retain your data for as long as you use the online services and for a reasonable time thereafter. If you’d like to delete, modify or update the data that you provided via the online services please use the settings on the online services or contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2f464149406f405a5b4a5d5f434e4c4a5c014c4042) and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of this data may be required in order for the online services to function properly, and we may be required to retain certain information by law.

* ## WHERE YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE USED

Outer Places, LLC is based in the United States and may from time to time transfer your personal information to other countries and make it accessible to any of our affiliates and third-party service providers internationally. Where the transfer of information is to a country which does not provide an adequate level of information protection, Outer Places, LLC has taken steps to ensure that your personal information receives an appropriate level of protection.

If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including personal information, may be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States. Under United States law, your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States.

By using our online services and providing your personal information to us you understand and agree that your personal information may be sent to other countries including those which do not provide an equivalent level of information protection as the European Economic Area (EEA).

* ## COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

Through our Cookies and Tracking Technologies policy, we provide opt-out choices. The effect of an opt-out will be to stop targeted advertising, but it will still allow the collection of usage data for certain purposes (e.g., research, analytics and internal online services operation purposes).

* ## IMPORTANT INFORMATION 

Notice to California Residents:

Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which our online service has disclosed certain personal information (as defined by California law) during the preceding year for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please contact us at Outer Places, 114 West 17th Street, 2nd Floor, NY, NY 10011. For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. In the body of your request, please provide enough information for us to determine if this applies to you. You need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone, email, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how Outer Places, LLC responds to "Do Not Track" browser settings. Outer Places, LLC does not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created.

Links to Other Websites:

This Privacy Policy only applies to our Website. Our Website may include links to the websites of third parties including, but not limited to, our business partners, vendors and advertisers. These other sites, their policies and practices, are outside of our control. Please be aware that these websites may collect information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices which may differ from those contained in our Privacy Policy. Remember to consult that website's own privacy policy, as once you are outside of our Website, any information you submit is no longer in our control.

* ## UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives, changes in the law or technology, or changes in our practices regarding information collection and use. If we make material revisions to the way we collect or use your personal information so that we are using it for purposes or sharing data with third parties that you have not consented to, we will provide you with notice of those changes and may do so by either: (1) announcing the change on the homepage of our website or (2) taking other actions as we deem appropriate under the circumstances, including without limitation, posting the revised version of this Privacy Policy online. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on our online services. You should check our online services frequently for updates.

You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the "Last Updated" or similar legend at the top of this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Internet, accessible through this site. By continuing to use this online service following such changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or in part, please do not continue using our online services.

* ## CONTACT US

For any queries in relation to this Privacy Policy please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2841464e4768475d5c4d5a5844494b4d5b064b4745) or Outer Places, 114 West 17th Street, 2nd Floor, NY, NY 10011.

On Outer Places, LLC online services, we along with our advertising partners and vendors, use a variety of technologies to learn more about how people use Outer Places, LLC online services. You can find out more about these technologies and how to control them in the information below. This policy forms part of the Outer Places, LLC Privacy Policy.

* ## COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES AND HOW WE USE THEM

Like many companies, we use Cookies and other Tracking Technologies on our online services (referred to together from this point forward as "Cookies", unless otherwise stated) which may include but are not limited to HTTP cookies, flash cookies, HTML5 and Flash local storage, web beacons/GIFs, embedded scripts, e-tags/cache browsers (as defined below).

We may use Cookies for a variety of purposes and to enhance your online experience, for example, by remembering your log¬in status and viewing preferences from a previous use of an online service, for when you later return to that online service. In particular, our online services use the following categories of Cookies:

  * Strictly Necessary Cookies: We may use Cookies required for system administration, to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to make use of shopping cart functionality. We are not required to obtain your consent to Cookies that are strictly necessary.

  * Analytics and Performance-Related Cookies: We may use Cookies to assess the performance of our online services, including as part of our analytic practices to improve the content offered through the online services.

  * Functionality-Related Cookies: We may use Cookies to tell us, for example, whether you have visited the online services before or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify the features in which you may have the greatest interest.

  * Targeting-Related Cookies: We may use Cookies to deliver content, including ads, relevant to your interests on our online service and third-party sites based on how you interact with our advertisements or content.

Your use of our services indicates your consent to such use of Cookies. For further information about our use of Cookies and your opt-out choices, see "Your Rights".

* ## USE OF COOKIES BY OUR ADVERTISING PARTNERS

The advertising networks and / or content providers that deliver ads on our online services may use Cookies to uniquely distinguish your web browser and keep track of information relating to serving ads on your web browser, such as the type of ads shown and the web pages on which the ads appeared.

Some of these companies may combine information they collect from our online services with other information they have independently collected relating to your web browser’s activities across their network of websites. These companies collect and use this information under their own privacy policies.

You may also opt out of additional third-party advertising networks by going to the Network Advertising Initiative’s Website at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) and following the directions there. The effect of opting out of third-party advertising networks is explained on each opt out page. Note that for some sites, the effect of opting out of third-party advertising means that customized advertising will not be delivered to you. Information regarding your usage of the online services may still be collected for research, analytics or internal operations purposes.

We are not responsible for the effectiveness of any such opt-out options.

California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how Outer Places, LLC responds to "Do Not Track" browser settings. Outer Places, LLC does not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created.

* ## YOUR COOKIE CHOICES AND HOW TO OPT OUT

You have the choice whether to accept the use of Cookies and we have explained how we can exercise your rights, as follows:

  * Most browsers are initially set up to accept HTTP cookies. The "help" feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, and how to disable existing cookies. For more information about HTTP cookies and how to disable them, or restrict the categories of cookies you wish to accept, you can consult the information at <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>

  * Controlling the HTML5 local storage on your browser depends on which browser you use. For more information regarding your specific browser please consult the browser’s website (often in the Help section).

  * For more information about Flash "cookies" or local storage objects or LSOs, and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided at <http://kb2.adobe.com/cps/526/52697ee8.html>

  * See "Use of Cookies by our Advertising Partners" for further information about how to opt out of Advertising Cookies. Please note that rejecting Cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our online services.

  * Please note, however, that without HTTP cookies and HTML5 and Flash local storage, you may not be able to take full advantage of all our online services features and some parts of the online services may not function properly.

* ## Definitions

**Cookies**

Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some but not all instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Please be aware that if you disable or remove cookies or HTML5 cookies on your device, some parts of our online services may not function properly, and that when you revisit our online service your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.

**Web Beacons**

Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including to count visitors to the online service, to monitor how users navigate the online services, to count how many e­mails we sent that were actually opened, or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to HTTP cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

**Embedded Script**

An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the online service, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device from our web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the online service, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

**ETag, or entity tag**

A feature of the cache in browsers, an ETag is an opaque identifier assigned by a web server to a specific version of a resource found at a URL. If the resource content at that URL ever changes, a new and different ETag is assigned. Used in this manner ETags are a form of device identifier. ETag tracking may generate unique tracking values even where the consumer blocks HTTP, Flash, and/or HTML5 cookies. 

* ## CONTACT US

For any queries in relation to this Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#92fbfcf4fdd2fde7e6f7e0e2fef3f1f7e1bcf1fdff) or Outer Places, Outer Places 49 W 37th Street, 15th Fl. New York, NY 10018.
